(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T18:00:11.601501",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
under moonlight we kiss goodbye
you walk off wearin' your disguise
give me something and don't think twice
and i told you all the things i would do
but does it matter when you
chase after pleasure you can't have?
now look where you ended up at
'cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
if you want it all i'll tell you now my love don't come for free
oh baby baby, yeah yeah yeah
you've got to treat me like a lady
cause i don't need no man to save me
boy i'll make you crazy
so look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
treat me like
ladylike
all your sweet talk and the flattery boy that shit don't fly!
i got 20/20 vision i see through every lie
stay deceivin' as you see fit you're just that type of guy
the stupid girls believe it but i'm another kind, oh
shoulda known that you'd get what was comin', boo
everything that you had wasn't meant for you
got 'em all lovesick like a virus
don't infect yourself this time
'cause out of seven billion people you won't find another me
if you wanna have it all then tell me what's it gonna be?
oh baby baby, yeah yeah yeah
you've got to treat me like a lady
i'll throw you out the way you came in, cause solitude don't faze me
so look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
and don't mess it up
cause all that you got is one chance to turn it around
and i've had enough, if you wanna earn it then work it, boy don't let me down
ba ba baby, yeah
you've got to treat me like a lady
cause i don't need no man to save me
boy i'll make you crazy
so look into my eyes and be real with me
oh baby baby, yeah
you've got to treat me like a lady
i'll throw you out the way you came in, cause solitude don't faze me
so look into my eyes and be real with me tonight
treat me like
ladylike
i'm alive, still breathing
stopped to hide, done grieving
realized that to survive someone's got to stand and fight
and i've tried to believe in
"only time stops the bleeding"
i'm not waiting anymore
i know what i came here for
'cuz feelings are temporary
but broken hearts keep the scars for life
the darkness no longer scares me
i'm chasing and hunting and this time i'm coming for blood
be the last one to laugh
when you run out of breath catching up
i'm a threat and a half, baby
you don’t even know me at all
i'm alive, still kicking
break the rules, rewrite the system
and my story wasn’t done, sharpened the knife and cocked the guns
cut the cord, burn the witch and you’ll regret what you’re missing
and i’ll take it to the grave, that’s the price that you pay, yeah
'cuz feelings are temporary
but broken hearts keep the scars for life
the darkness no longer scares me
i'm chasing and hunting and this time i'm coming for blood
And this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh
When you run out of breath
Catching up
I'm a threat and a half, baby
You don't even know me at all
I'm alive, still kicking
Break the rules, rewrite the system
'Cuz feelings are temporary
But broken hearts keep the scars for life
The darkness no longer scares me
I'm chasing and hunting
And this time I'm coming for blood
Be the last one to laugh
When you run out of breath
Catching up
I'm a threat and a half, baby
You don't even know me at all
Be the last one to laugh
When you run out of breath
Catching up
I'm a threat and a half, baby
You don't even know me at all
Yaaay!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
And well, welcome everybody, first of all, to my concert!
I hope you enjoyed the first two songs! How was it?
Thank you, thank you, thank you! I hope I already got you hyped up!
This is going to be a really fun show,
but a fun show also needs some special guests, some people to talk to, maybe some call-ins, some games.
And don't worry, I got you covered. I have invited a very special friend to play a very special game together with.
And my friend is none other than my Otonashi... member, Nenetchi!
Yaaay! Can you hear me?
Happy birthday, Kiara-chan! Nenetchi!
Thank you! That's right, it's my birthday.
I almost forgot,
Nenetchi, can you introduce yourself in English, please?
Sure!
hololive 5th Generation, Momosuzu Nene!
Yay!
Thank you for coming! Thanks for having me!
So...
So Nenetchi and I will be playing "Idol Shiritori"!
It's a brilliant game that I came up with. Yay! That's right!
After all, if I'm the top idol in hololive English, then for hololive Japan, it would have to be Nenetchi!
Gosh, thank you!
Nenetchi is hololive Japan's number one idol in my heart, so I thought that the following game would be very fitting.
So I thought up this game. The rules are the following. First of all, the name is "Idol Shiritori". The normal shiritori works the following...
I say a Japanese word, and they usually are built up in syllables. So the syllable that it ends with, Nenetchi will have to think of... a new word that it starts with that syllable. And then we keep on connecting and connecting until someone makes a mistake... or says a word that already has been said.
But, here is the twist!
We can only use idol words, or cute or girly words, feminine words.
So anything that's cutesy and idol... Yeah, I think... us too, we shouldn't have any issues with that.
Idol Shiritori should be a piece of cake for us, right?
We can do it! Okay, then let's give it a shot!
Okay! Nenechi, you ready? Ready! Let's try to keep the pace up.
Okay! All right! Here we go! Start! Start!
dokidoki (exciting)
ki... kirakira (sparkling)
から始めよう
Okay, you start, Nenechi.
オッケー。じゃあ、好きなタイミングで。どうぞ。
Okay. Whenever you're ready, go ahead.
ネネチ
Nenechi!
ち…ち…ち…ちいず
Chi... chi... chi... chiizu (cheese)
ず…ちいずふぉんじゅ
Zu... chiizu fondyu (cheese fondue)
ああ、いいね！可愛いね。チーフォン…デュ？
Ah, good one. Very cute, no? Chee-fon... dyu?
デュ？あぁ難しいな。デュで？ユー？ユー？
Dyu? Right, that's a hard one. You can use yu. Yu? Yu?
オッケー、ゆ…ゆびわ
Okay, yu... yubiwa (ring)
おお！ワンダフル！
Oh! Wandafuru! (Wonderful!)
ル…ルビー！
Ru... rubii! (Ruby!)
う…び…びなす…
Uh... bi... biinasu! (Venus!)
す…す…す…す…す…するめ
Su... su... su... su... su... surume (dried squid)
えっ？するめって…魚？するめは、うん、おつまみ。
What? Isn't that a type of fish? It's a type of... drinking snack?
いや、可愛いことない！可愛い言葉思いつかんかった！
Okay, that is not! I couldn't think of anything cute! That's not cute!
ブーブー！ブーブー！
Bzzzt! Bzzzt!
え、すから始まる可愛い言葉何？逆に。え、スクール水着？
Is there something cute that starts with su? Hm? Sukuuru mizugi! (School swimsuit)
ああ、可愛いわ！
Oh, that is cute!
え、まあこの時点で勝ちなんだけど、ワンモアやる？
Well, it looks like I win already, but wanna do one more?
うん、次3ポイントにしない？
Let's make the next round three points.
3ポイント？次勝ったらネネチ…いや、次勝ったら…同点、同点！で、もう平和な終わり方。
Three points? If you win the next round, then... A tie? Okay, sure, it's a tie. So nobody loses in the end!
え、そうしよう、そうしよう。
Sounds good! Okay, great.
じゃあ、次ウチから始めます。はい。せーの！
Then I'll start the next round. Here I go. Se-no!
フラミンゴ！
Furamingo! (Flamingo)
うん…あ…ご…ゴールテープ！
Um... go... gooruteepu! (Finish line ribbon)
えっ？何時、何時それ？え？英語じゃないのか？
Wait, what's that? What'd you say? I dunno what it is in English.
ゴールテープ？ゴールテープ？あ、ゴールテープ！
Gorepu? Gooruteepu! Oh, gooruteepu!
運動会の最後のやつ。可愛いか？可愛いか！まあ、オッケーオッケー！すすむよ、うん。
The thing at the end of a race! Is that cute? It is totally cute! Okay, we'll count it! It counts! Let's keep going.
え？あ、じゃあプ？プ…プ…プ、プ、プ…プ…プ、プ…プアンデリング？
Hm? Oh, so next is pu? Pu... pu... pu... pu... puanderingu? (Mochi donut)
プアンデリング？！うーん…あったよね、そういうの。あったよね？
Puanderingu?! Hmm... That's a thing right? Right?
ぐ…ぐ…ぐ…ぐ、ぐ、ぐ…ぐ…ぐ…ぐ…グーテンモルゲン、キアラ！
Gu... gu... gu... gu... gu, gu... gu... Guten Morgen, Kiara!
え？！グーテンモルゲン、キアラ？！
What?! Guten Morgen, Kiara?
ランドセル！ランドセル！あ、いいね！順調、順調！
Randoseru! (Child's backpack) Ooh, good one! Doing good, doing good!
る…る…る？ルッコラ？ルッコラ？わからんけど、オッケーオッケー。
Ru... ru... ru? Rukkora? (Arugula) Dunno what that is, but sure!
ら…ラミー！先輩！
Ra... Ramii-senpai!
い…い…い…い…い…い…い…い…いぬ！
I... i... i... i... i... i... inu! (Dog)
お…ぬ…ぬ…ぬ…ぬ…ぬ…ぬ！！！わからんよ、ネネチ！
Oh... nu... nu... nu... nu... nu... nu! I can't think of anything, Nenechi!
はあ、分かった。負けたよ。そんで、平和な終わり方やん。やった！
Okay, fine. I lost! And with that! We end the game tied! Yay!
一番、一番いいのでは。そうかもしれない。
I think it's best this way, probably for the best!
Because I lost, so we decided that we both... we both win in the end. Yes. Well, I may have won twice and she may have won once.
But in the end, we're Oreinds, so all is good. We love each other. World is beautiful, world is peace. Yay!
とういうことでネネチありがとうございました！またね、グッバイ！
Okay, thanks for coming, Nenechi! Thank you! Good-bye!
あ、今度はね、オレンジで二人で踊ろう！そうしよう！バイバイ！シーユーネネチ！
Oh, let's get together as the Oreinds sometime and dance! Yeah, let's! Bye-bye! See you, Nenechi!
さあ、次の曲！
So, let's go to the next song!
lying down on the floor
late night and you don't know, don't know
don't know what to do
hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
if yes or no, don't know
don't know what to do
the storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head, life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it if you want it
Let's get to it, everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid, just trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano, strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table, to the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it, you heard what I said
Get out of your head, life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So take a step and move it, move it
'Less you try you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid, just trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
From the ashes you rise
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
So don't be afraid, just trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Gonna make it hot like a volcano, strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table, to the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
Ah yeah
Hello, nice to meet ya, my name is perfection
I come from the net inside your personal computer
A tool for the dreamers, make you a believer
I'm so worldwide, worldwide, holy virtual diva
But sometimes I do-don't you?
Think of the things they told you
There must be more than this, there must be more than what you know too
I wasn't made to feel, but lately, I can't help it
If there's a way out of here, I've got an idea
Break it all down, I'll make you come around
I'll burn this whole façade to the ground
I'm so sick of windows, I need something physical
Hah, tough luck in a digital world
Whine about your issues, what your life has come to
Sure, alright, I got it, poor you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real
Singing "ah, life sucks as a digital girl!"
So, I woke up with a headache today
Just kidding, I don't feel pain
To be honest, I don't even gotta sleep
And that's the difference between you and me
And I know, I know, I know, I know, everybody wants it
Til they gotta commit
Looking through my eyes, change your mind so quick
You won't believe the sh-- I've seen, and
No day is like the other, be anything I wanna
There is no suffering, wars or existential crisis drama
But I feel something inside of my "heart"
And it's telling me to go before I fall apart
Break it all down, I'll make you come around
I'll burn this whole façade to the ground
I'm so sick of windows, I need something physical
Hah, tough luck in a digital world
Whine about your issues, what your life has come to
Sure, alright, I got it, poor you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real!
Singing "ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
Hello, nice to meet ya, my name is perfection
I come from the net inside your personal computer
A tool for the dreamers, make you a believer
I’m so worldwide, worldwide
I'm so worldwide, worldwide
Holy virtual diva
But sometimes I do-don't you? Think of the things they told you
There must be more than this, there must be more than what you know too
I wasn’t made to feel, but lately, I can’t help it
I wasn't made to feel, but lately, I can't help it
If there’s a way out of here, I’ve got an idea
If there's a way out of here, I've got an idea
Break it all down, I’ll make you come around
Break it all down, I'll make you come around
I’ll burn this whole façade to the ground
I'll burn this whole façade to the ground
I’m so sick of windows, I need something physical
I'm so sick of windows, I need something physical
Hah, tough luck in a digital world
Whine about your issues, what your life has come to
Sure, alright, I got it, poor you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real
Singing "Ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
Break it all down, I’ll make you come around
Break it all down, I'll make you come around
I’ll burn this whole façade to the ground
I'll burn this whole façade to the ground
I’m so sick of windows, I need something physical
I'm so sick of windows, I need something physical
Hah, tough luck in a digital world
Whine about your issues, what your life has come to
Sure, alright, I got it, poor you
How do you think I feel? None of this is real
Singing "Ahh, life sucks as a digital girl!"
The Bigaku / Matsuura Aya
[Title: The Bigaku / Matsuura Aya]
告白 出来ないで
Without being able to confess,
凹んじゃった見っともない
feeling down and looking pathetic,
あいつはカッチョ前の優しい男
he's a cool and gentle guy.
ダラダラやってないですぐ行こうぜ midnight
Don't drag things out, let's go right away midnight!
baby 言う事はいっちょ前の
Baby, talking big like an adult,
もう一人の私
I am my other self.
恋しているから切ないけど
I'm in love, so it hurts so much,
愛し合ってても cry! cry! cry!
even though we love each other, cry! cry! cry!
恋する女とその男の美学
The aesthetics of a loving woman and that man.
朝目覚めたらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
When I wake up in the morning, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魅力
The charm of a loving man and that woman.
寂しい夜は涙流してもそれでいいんだよ
On lonely nights, even if you shed tears, that's fine.
告白出来ないで
Without being able to confess,
凹んじゃった見っともない
feeling down and looking pathetic,
あいつはカッチョ前の優しい男
he's a cool and gentle guy.
ダラダラやってないですぐ行こうぜ midnight
Don't drag things out, let's go right away midnight!
baby 言う事はいっちょ前の
Baby, talking big like an adult,
もう一人の私
I am my other self.
恋しているから切ないけど
I'm in love, so it hurts so much,
愛し合ってても cry! cry! cry!
even though we love each other, cry! cry! cry!
恋する女とその男の美学
The aesthetics of a loving woman and that man.
親族皆相談 結婚式の実際
Consulting all our relatives on the wedding's reality,
あいつは優柔不断の可愛い男
he's an indecisive, cute guy.
キラキラ midnight so dance
Sparkling midnight so dance!
恋しちゃって頂戴 baby 覚悟は半人前のもう一人の私
Falling in love, baby, my resolution is half-baked, my other self.
都内で夢見る恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city, a lazy afternoon of love.
世の中気合いで右・肩・上がり
In this world, with spirit, heads held high!
恋する女とその男の化学
The chemistry of a loving woman and that man.
反応したらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
Once there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魔力
The magic of a loving man and that woman.
孤独な夜は二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us dream without parting.
恋する女とその男の化学
The chemistry of a loving woman and that man.
反応したらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
Once there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魔力
The magic of a loving man and that woman.
孤独な夜は二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us dream without parting.
都内で夢見る恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city, a lazy afternoon of love.
世の中気合いで右・肩・上がり
In this world, with spirit, heads held high!
恋する女とその男の化学
The chemistry of a loving woman and that man.
反応したらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
Once there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魔力
The magic of a loving man and that woman.
孤独な夜は二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us dream without parting.
都内で夢見る恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city, a lazy afternoon of love.
世の中気合いで右・肩・上がり
In this world, with spirit, heads held high!
恋する女とその男の化学
The chemistry of a loving woman and that man.
反応したらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
Once there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魔力
The magic of a loving man and that woman.
孤独な夜は二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us dream without parting.
都内で夢見る恋の昼下がり
Dreaming in the city, a lazy afternoon of love.
世の中気合いで右・肩・上がり
In this world, with spirit, heads held high!
恋する女とその男の化学
The chemistry of a loving woman and that man.
反応したらそこで kiss & kiss & kiss
Once there's a reaction, kiss & kiss & kiss right there!
恋する男とその女の魔力
The magic of a loving man and that woman.
孤独な夜は二人離れずに夢を見るんだよ
On lonely nights, the two of us dream without parting.
デビきゅー デビきゅー
Devi kyu-, devi kyu-
デビきゅー デビきゅーと
Devi kyu-, devi kyu- to!
よし！今日こそ決めるわ！
Alright! I'm gonna nail it today!
髪型チェック！スカートはたいてい
Hair check! Fluff my skirt!
きみに褒められる準備は万端！
I'm all set to receive your compliments!
そでをつかんだらキュンとする？
Will you feel a flutter if I grab your sleeve?
つまさきふれたらドキッとするかしら？
Will you be startled if our toes touch?
かわいいって言わせちゃおう
My plan to make you say I'm cute is foolproof!
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
髪型もバッチリOK
Hair looking bouncin' and O.K.!
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
Gotta do my best on Friday,
だって二日会えないからね
'Cause I won't see you for two whole days!
8:00零分二車両目お気に入りの特等席
8:00 AM, car number two, my favorite special seat
隣の人眠そうですねそんな日常
The person next to me looks so sleepy, just an everyday routine
8:07開くのは向かいのドア息を潜め
8:07 AM, the opposite door opens, I hold my breath
言いかけてた「その言葉」は今日も逃げた
The words I meant to say slipped away again today
きっかけシンプルでいいのに意気地ないな
A simple reason would be fine, but I'm just too chicken
勇気のテスト乗り越えなくちゃ逃げなくちゃって
Gotta pass this courage test, no running away...
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
弱虫な自分に勝って
Winning against my cowardly self
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
Gotta do my best on Friday,
だって二日会えないからね
'Cause I won't see you for two whole days!
眠そうな君を見てる
Just watching you looking sleepy
それだけで満足しちゃって
Makes me so satisfied already
ダメだって「頑張らなくちゃ」そっと声に出してみた
No, I gotta do my best! I whispered out loud to myself
8:00零分二車両目座られてた特等席
8:00 AM, car number two, my special seat was taken
ついてないな空模様まで泣きそうで
How unlucky, even the weather looks like it's gonna cry
8:07準備まだ、ちょっと待ってドキドキが…
8:07 AM, not ready yet, wait a second, my heart is racing...
震え混ざり「その言葉」かき消された
Mixed with a tremor, "those words" were completely drowned out
雨降り立ち尽くす僕に「傘をどうぞ」
Seeking shelter from the rain, standing there, "Here, take my umbrella"
君は少し恥ずかしそうに下を向いた
You lowered your gaze, looking a little embarrassed
「ありがとう」震えていた
"Thank you," your voice was trembling
練習していない言葉言えたから頑張らなくちゃ
I said words I hadn't practiced, so I gotta do my best,
だって二日会えないからね
'Cause I won't see you for two whole days!
大好きな君を見てる
Watching you whom I love so dearly
それだけじゃ満足できなくて
Just that isn't enough anymore
月曜日頑張らなくちゃ
Gotta do my best on Monday!
そっと声に出してみた
I whispered out loud to myself
夢では自然に話せるのに
Even though I can talk naturally in my dreams
勇気のテスト乗り越えるから少し待ってて
I'll overcome this courage test, so please wait a little longer!
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
髪型もバッチリOK
Hair looking bouncin' and O.K.!
8:07に君を待ってるだって今日は言えるから
Waiting for you at 8:07 AM, 'Cause I can say it today!
おやすみも言いたいだけれどちょっと待って
I want to say goodnight too, but wait a minute...
大好きな言葉なんだ
It's my most beloved phrase
だって君に会えるからね
'Cause it means I get to see you!
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
髪型もバッチリOK
Hair looking bouncin' and O.K.!
金曜日は頑張らなくちゃ
Gotta do my best on Friday,
だって二日会えないからね
'Cause I won't see you for two whole days!
眠そうな君を見てる
Just watching you looking sleepy
それだけで満足しちゃって
Makes me so satisfied already
ダメだって「頑張らなくちゃ」そっと声に出してみた
No, I gotta do my best! I whispered out loud to myself
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
髪型もバッチリOK
Hair looking bouncin' and O.K.!
大好きな君を見てる
Watching you whom I love so dearly
それだけじゃ満足しなくて
Just that isn't enough anymore
金曜日頑張らなくちゃ
Gotta do my best on Friday!
そっと声に出してみた
I whispered out loud to myself
おはようのオーディションして
Doing my morning audition
髪型もバッチリOK
Hair looking bouncin' and O.K.!
8:07に君を待ってる
Waiting for you at 8:07 AM
だって今日ば言えるからお休みも言いたいけれど
'Cause I can say it today! I want to say goodnight too, but
ちょっと待って大好きな言葉なんだ
wait a minute, it's my most beloved phrase
だって君に会えるからね
'Cause it means I get to see you!
All right, everybody! How was that? Did you like...
the previous songs? It was...
Debikaku from Matsurika-ya and Kinyoubi no Ohayou from HoneyWorks, yeah!
Um, especially the... Debikaku...
I was really excited to perform for you guys because it's a hellodj project song...
that probably a lot of you guys don't know, but did you like it? Did you like it? Did you like it?
It's pretty cool. Yeah!
Matsurika-ya is good! So...
next up, we will have more guests, more guests, more guests...
Guess who? Previously was none other than Chi,
Guess who? Previously it was none other than Chi,
who could possibly be my next guest?
What do you think, guys?
Well, more friends are coming!
None other than my beloved third duck and hololive member,
Oozora Subaru!
and Pavolia Reine!
Happy birthday!
Thank you! Thank you!
We're so happy! Thank you for coming, for flying over here like the birds you are.
Well, I'm already doing gestures, but I wonder what are we doing with you guys?
Oh, what could it be? Charades!
We're playing charades!
The typical game that you have to play when you're in 3D.
Well, I think we have like a synergy, HoloTori synergy, so whatever movement I do, you will understand, right?
Yes, of course! Okay, of course!
Okay, actually, the words are provided by none other than Subaru, who is so far behind the scenes.
So she will feed me the words, I will act them out, and you guys will guess them.
So, shall we begin? Yeah!
Snail!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go!
Cat! Dog! Animal!
Turtle! Turtle!
Oh, almost!
Labbie?
Slow! Slow!
Long! Long!
Snake!
Breathe here!
Slimey! Slimey!
Slimy! Slimy!
It's slimy? Slimy? Slimy?
Snail! Snail!
Snail!
Yay!
Okay, next! Snail!
Katatsumuri! Yes! Katatsumuri! Yes! Snail!
Snail backwards!
Tooth brush!
Toothbrush!
Brush my teeth!
With? With toothbrush!
With a toothbrush! Yes!
Next!
Ping pong!
Catchball!
Baseball!
Wakatta!
Ping pong! Ping pong!
That's right!
Next!
KFP!
Chicken! Phoenix!
A juggling?
Kid! Circus!
Kid! Kid!
Dance, kid, dance!
Chicken dance! KFP! KFP!
Okay, okay, okay, last word!
Okay, last word is...
Chicken dance!
Chicken dance! Chicken!
Everybody must chicken dance! Yes!
Idol! Idol! Idol Kiara!
Idol chicken dance!
Idol! Idol! Idol chicken!
Chicken!
No! No! No!
Pretty, pretty hip!
Uh, daburazu? No, no, no.
Uh, double jump? No, no, no.
Pretty hip!
Kiara, pretty dance!
No, Kiara!
Oodoriru? Matsuri? Maririn?
Yuyu! Yuyu! Yuyu!
Okay, okay! Wait! One more! One more! You! You! You!
Me
Huh?
Yumi?
Ah no.
Wait.
Lady!
I've been...
I lost.
So Yuzu-senpai, yo! Yuzu-senpai!
Me! Me! It's Yuzu-senpai!
This is... this is the Duck! The Duck then!
Duck! Duck! Duck! Duck!
How can you not know?!
I'm sorry!
Now I see it! Now I see it!
Yeah, now you see!
So you're shaking your hip!
Yeah! But it's okay!
We still did four out of five!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Turdukin is best!
Turdukin! Let's go!
Thank you very much for coming!
Yameka!
Thank you!
I love you! I love you!
Love you, bye-bye!
FEVER NIGHT
Takanashi Kiara
i'm tired of the same song
everyday like it's on repeat
i need a risque breakdown
I need a risqué breakdown
oh honey, the night is calling
don't need a steady simple melody
can you make it original?
take me away like it's just the two of us
i'm ready, do you feel the music?
baby
meet me underneath the strobe light
come alive
move my feet to something new
i don't need no drinks tonight
gimme that beat get me dancing
(feel it rush through me)
let this new sound take over me
(intoxicating, dj keep playing)
lately i'm dancing alone
so robotic so emotionless
but then i see you across the dance floor
so now honey follow me
i need a thrilling red-hot melody
something to keep me up all night
don't look away, now it's just the two of us
i'm ready, do you feel the music?
baby
meet me underneath the strobe light
come alive
move my feet to something new
i don't need no drinks tonight
gimme that beat get me dancing
(feel it rush through me)
この心の音を
Connect this heart's sound,
合わせて yeah follow my heart beat
matching it, yeah, follow my heartbeat.
bada da da da da da da di da
聞かせてあげる 心の bada ba badi
letting you hear my heart's bada ba badi,
合わせて follow my heart beat
matching it, follow my heartbeat.
crazy for your rhythm
i'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
you got me shining glowing like a prism
that disco ball makes me wild don't care who's watching us
so baby
meet me underneath the strobe light
come alive
movin' my feet to something so new
i don't need no drinks tonight
gimme that beat get me dancing
(feel it rush through me)
i don't need no drinks tonight
gimme that beat get me dancing
(feel it rush through me)
baby, can we dance until the daylight
crazy 'bout this sound i'm making with you
まばたく星のゆりかご 欠けたセリフを
The cradle of twinkling stars, the broken lines
つなぎ合わせたmemory
Pieced together into memory
聖なる従者が伝える神話の理
The holy follower conveys the myth's truth
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Tuning our ears to the prayer
Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
Tell me 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
荒ぶる心音は傷を焦がす
The raging heartbeat scorches the wound.
揺振り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Yielding my body to the swaying, pouring skies,
乱れ咲く紅は紅化粧
The blooming crimson is rouge makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いて見せる
Surviving countless trials to show you,
I will live to keep on fighting 'till the dawn
たとさえきの見えないゼロの境界
Even at the invisible zero boundary,
迷い込んだとしても
Even if I stray inside,
何度も繰り返される孤高の終焉
The solitary end that repeats time and again,
そこに残ったanswer
The answer left behind there.
Don't break, I will never give up,
Don't break 羽根が朽ちても
Don't break, even if my feathers decay,
消えない強さは時のしるべ
An unfading strength is the guide of time.
灰かまいあがる大地身をくぐらせ
Shaking off the rising ash across the land,
萌ゆる明けのなか目を覚ます
Waking up amidst the sprouting dawn.
刀交わる剣先 交わした契りは
The crossing tips of blades, the vow we exchanged—
Lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
Tell me 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
みなぎる決意は影を晴らす
A surging determination clears away the shadows.
揺振り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Yielding my body to the swaying, pouring skies,
乱れ咲く紅は紅化粧
The blooming crimson is rouge makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いて見せる
Surviving countless trials to show you,
Blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
And in the next life too I promise, I will find you
聖なる従者が伝える神話の理
The holy follower conveys the myth's truth
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Tuning our ears to the prayer
Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
Tell me 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
荒ぶる心音は傷を焦がす
The raging heartbeat scorches the wound.
揺振り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Yielding my body to the swaying, pouring skies,
乱れ咲く紅は紅化粧
The blooming crimson is rouge makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いて見せる
Surviving countless trials to show you,
I will live to keep on fighting 'till the dawn
たとさえきの見えないゼロの境界
Even at the invisible zero boundary,
迷い込んだとしても
Even if I stray inside,
何度も繰り返される孤高の終焉
The solitary end that repeats time and again,
そこに残ったanswer
The answer left behind there.
Don't break, I will never give up,
Don't break 羽根が朽ちても
Don't break, even if my feathers decay,
消えない強さは時のしるべ
An unfading strength is the guide of time.
灰かまいあがる大地身をくぐらせ
Shaking off the rising ash across the land,
萌ゆる明けのなか目を覚ます
Waking up amidst the sprouting dawn.
刀交わる剣先 交わした契りは
The crossing tips of blades, the vow we exchanged—
Lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
Tell me 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice,
みなぎる決意は影を晴らす
A surging determination clears away the shadows.
揺振り注ぐ空に身をやつして
Yielding my body to the swaying, pouring skies,
乱れ咲く紅は紅化粧
The blooming crimson is rouge makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いて見せる
Surviving countless trials to show you,
Blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
And in the next life too I promise, I will find you
Yay! How was that?
Yeah, we just for the first time ever performed 'Fever Night' and 'HINOTORI'.
Yeah, we just performed 'Fever Night' and 'HINOTORI' for the very first time!
Yeah, the classic HINOTORI—I bet you all wanted to see it once again.
But Fever Night is a new, very new, my newest single, so I hope you're listening to it a lot!
Are you? Of course, KFP is always streaming Kiara's songs.
Thank you very much for your support! So, you thought that was done with Calliope's... huh?
No, no, no, no, there's more! There's more, there's more!
Aren't we missing certain Myth members?
Mhm.
Yes, we are!
Of course we are!
So, please come and say hello to
Gura and Callie!
I I I wouldn't do...
Happy birthday, Kiara! Happy birthday!
Thank you!
You are a birthday—
You could say it's not my birthday, but it's my burth-day! Burth-burth-burth...
Ah, I get it. You made a funny word joke.
Sasuga 3D show. Looking so cute.
You know, you're finally, finally like I can do my whole I can show off my body in 3D, like for a whole stream. Yeah! It's so detailed and beautiful.
You know, you're finally... like I can do my whole— I can show off my body in 3D, like for a whole stream. Yeah! It's so detailed and beautiful.
Oh, thank you. Which Which part do you like? In 3D, it's very nice. What's what's your what's your favorite part?
Oh, thank you. Which part do you like? In 3D it's very nice. What's what's your favorite part?
It's tummy window.
Uh, I love the little wings back.
Yeah.
Yeah, the bows too, right?
You can see that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can only see that in 3D, you know.
Right? And the little wings too, our expressions are...
Oh, cute.
Yeah.
So you're going to pull out your sword? You're going to get your sword out someday for us?
Oh, that's a good question.
Well, maybe another time. Maybe, maybe at a 3D debut stream, which this is not. Right? Yeah.
All right. Well, girls, we are the same generation, so one would assume that you know a finger or two about me, right? Yeah. Of course.
We've only met many times. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Especially us, yes, yes.
But also me and Gura have now met in real life, thankfully. Yay! Yes, that's true.
You have hopefully a lot of knowledge about me and I will test that with...
The Kiara-Wawa quiz! Kiara-Wawa quiz, let's go! Yay! Boom boom boom boom!
Woo hoo hoo hoo! Skrah!
I have five questions for you, girls.
And if you answer at least four of the questions correctly, then I shall take you out to dinner sometime.
Oh, cool.
Can you ask for a prize? Of course there's a prize! Yeah, there's always a prize at KFP.
So, are you ready for the first question? Get it on.
By the way, you can work together if you want.
Audit it?
Yeah, let's do it. Yeah, put the two the two the two biggest brains in Hololive Myth together.
Yeah, let's do it. Yeah, put the two— the two biggest brains in Hololive Myth together.
What do you call yourselves again? The Boneheads? No. Bone Bros.
Bone Bros will solve all the questions! Bone heads and feathers. Now, we got this unlocked. It's just math. Just don't ask us about math.
I don't even know math either.
So, our first question, are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
This is easy.
Question number one, what does KFP stand for?
Kyutaro Fried Phoenix.
Oh!
Kiara Fried Phoenix!
No, no, no, no, Kiarafried!
Did you say Kiara Kentucky?
No, and I and I've never heard of that place. I said Kiara. You guys misheard. Sorry.
No, and I've never heard of that place. I said Kiara. You guys misheard. Sorry.
That's your problem.
I said Kiara Fried Phoenix. I I know KFP. I've eaten KFP before.
I should almost give you a minus point for that answer.
No, no, no, no, please don't take away my my degree in Kiarology, please. I beg you.
Okay, I'll give you the point. That was easy though.
All right, next question, I wrote it down. What is it? Ah, yeah, okay.
Question number two. Okay.
Imagine some quiz lights, quiz quiz show lights. Yeah.
What was, okay, a new rule, I will only allow correct answers if you had one, if you lock in one wrong answer, that's's a no point.
What was— okay, a new rule, I will only allow correct answers if you had one— if you lock in one wrong answer, that's a no point!
All right, girl, don't fuck this up.
All right, so question number two. What was Takanashi Kiara's second original single?
Heart Challenger.
Yes! That was going to say that too! Let's go!
Sorry, Gumbis. You need to give her some time to shine. Kiara needs to shine.
Okay, Gura, the next one's yours.
I'll be faster.
I'm leaving the hard ones for Gura, actually. It's all part of my plan.
By the way, what was Kiara's first original song, by the way? Extra question. Hinotori!
Wait, my first, my third? Did you probably acoustically... Oh, I thought you said first.
Sorry, I can't... Yeah, my my TH always sounds like an F.
Sorry, I can't... Yeah, my TH
always sounds like an F.
It's okay, it's cute.
My... number three of my song was... but that sounds close.
My... number three of my song
was... but that sounds close.
Sparks? Yes, okay. Good, good.
Sparks, let the flame! Woo! Listen out, listen out!
Sparks, let the flame! Woo!
Listen out, listen out!
Dance up, dance up, just go up and down!
Dance up, dance up,
just go up and down!
Okay, no, that was not the first question. The first question is coming now. Can I see it? It was... uh... Okay.
Okay, no, that was not the first question.
The first question is coming now. Can I see it? It was... uh... Okay.
Okay, now this one, let's see. Question number three, done done done!
Okay, now this one, let's see.
Question number three, dun dun dun!
What's the name of the mouse/slash rat that I lived with in Japan?
What's the name of the mouse/rat
that I lived with in Japan?
I know this. I'm going to let Gura answer.
I know this. I'm going
to let Gura answer.
Yeah, let's see.
Uff, I feel like I've been told this before. Oh shit.
Ugh, I feel like I've been
told this before. Oh shit.
If you know this, oh no.
Oh, do you need to phone a friend?
Okay, Casper.
Kelly, Kelly!
Calli, Calli!
Sorry! I can't help myself!
It's okay! You give the easy ones, man.
It's okay! You give the
easy ones, man.
Actually, just recently... Just recently, I uploaded a video, uh, a lore video that explains the whole story behind Casper on my channel,
Actually, just recently...
I uploaded a lore video that explains
the whole story behind Casper on my channel,
so if you guys are curious, you could go watch that if you want to learn more about Casper mysterious, yes. Casper the friendly... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
so if you want to learn more about
Casper the friendly... ghost. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
First I hated him, then I loved him. Okay!
First I hated him, then I loved him.
Okay!
Fourth question! If you get this one right, then you already have a free dinner with me!
Fourth question! If you get this one right,
you already have a free dinner with me!
Thank you for caring, Calli.
Yeah, no problem. No, you- No, you got this, girl. You definitely got the next one.
Yeah, no problem. No, you- No, you got this, girl.
You definitely got the next one.
Dude, I don't know if I do, girl. You don't know? I do. I do.
Dude, I don't know if I do, girl. You don't know?
I do. I do.
Okay, question number four, ja ja ja! (dun dun dun)
Okay, question number four, dun dun dun!
How many re-debuts did Takanashi Kiara have? Now think before you yell it out loud.
How many re-debuts did Takanashi Kiara have?
Now think before you yell it out loud.
Re-debuts? Re-debuts? Mmm.
Wait, what counts as a re-debut? Well, a not debut, but debuts after the re-debut.
Wait, what counts as a re-debut?
Well, not debuts, but debuts after the re-debut.
I do have a history with re-debuts. It hasn't been one in a while, but there was a time where I had many reasons for many re-debuts.
I do have a history with re-debuts. It hasn't been
one in a while, but there was a time where
I had many reasons for many re-debuts.
Man... My brain used to say two, but I don't know.
Man... My brain used to say two,
but I don't know.
Okay, girl, let's brainstorm. All right.
So you have 10 more seconds. Oh shit, you remember.
So you have 10 more seconds.
Oh shit, you remember.
When the first one? When the channel got... The next one was the German one, right?
The first one, when the channel got...
The next one was the German one, right?
Right! Wait, wait, wait, wait, it's two.
Okay, so I think it's two.
You are feeling it's two.
You're feeling it's two.
Are you sure? Yeah.
Oh, I think it's two.
Correct, dancers! Yeah!
Woo! Good job!
Well, okay, okay. Well, mmm, I still have one more question though.
Well, okay, okay. Well, mmm,
I still have one more question though.
You're a winner, chicken dinner.
From the chicken, let's go! I think we're four for four so far.
From the chicken, let's go!
I think we're four for four so far.
Yes, we are. But I guess my questions were a little bit too easy.
Yes, we are. But I guess my questions
were a little bit too easy.
So, the next question you will have to answer correctly otherwise, otherwise...
So, the next question you will have to
answer correctly, otherwise, otherwise...
Ah, damn it. It will not be, yeah, it will be...
Ah, damn it. It will not be...
Yeah, it will be...
Changing the rules on us.
Can we double down?
Do we get dessert too?
Of course, of course!
Excellent. Excellent. Last question and...
Excellent. Excellent.
Last question and...
how should we do this? Mmm, I want your separate answers.
how should we do this?
Mmm, I want your separate answers.
So... What happened? Wait, we was changing the... Okay.
So... what happened? Wait, we were changing the...
Okay.
Now, I just want to see if you both get it right without hearing the other's answer first.
Now, I just want to see if you both get it right
without hearing the other's answer first.
Okay.
I'll take off my headphones.
Okay, okay, okay. Man, uh...
how do I give you a sign that you should come back? Whatever, just bring it back in in 30 seconds, okay?
How do I give you a sign that you should come back?
Whatever, just bring it back in 30 seconds, okay?
Okay, do like throw up like some kind of weird like hand symbol. Ah, okay, I'll do this. Do a little heart. Yeah, and then I'll come back. All right, bye.
Okay, do like throw up some kind of weird
hand symbol. Ah, okay, I'll do this. Do a little heart.
Yeah, and then I'll come back. All right, bye.
I'm taking off my headphones. Bye.
Bye.
Go, go, Gura.
I actually have a feeling you'll get this one right.
I actually have a feeling
you'll get this one right.
Really? Okay.
Spell out for me without thinking too much, you have to say it quickly.
Spell out for me without thinking too much.
You have to say it quickly.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Go! Auf... a-u-f... auf... a-u-f... Wiedersehen. V-i-e-d-e-r-s-e-h-e-n... s-e-u-n... s-e-u-n... s-e-n... auf... da... a-u-f... auf is the first part.
Go! Auf... a-u-f... auf... a-u-f...
Wiedersehen. V-i-e-d-e-r-s-e-h-e-n...
s-e-u-n... s-e-u-n... s-e-n...
auf... da... a-u-f... auf is the first part.
Wieder... Wiedersehen. V-i-e-d-e-r-s... e-n-s-e... It's hard to follow you. It's hard to follow you.
Wieder... Wiedersehen.
V-i-e-d-e-r-s... e-n-s-e...
It's hard to follow you. It's hard to follow you.
Final answer, go!
A-U-F... Mhmm... V... Mhmm... I-E-D-E-R-S-E-E-N...
A-U-F... Mhmm...
V... Mhmm...
I-E-D-E-R-S-E-E-N...
Wrong!
No!
Okay, Kelly, come back. Kelly, come back. All I heard was wrong.
Okay, Calli, come back. Calli, come back.
All I heard was wrong!
Is it that hard of a question?
Throw it at me, Kiara.
Now, Kelly... Kelly recently... um... had...
Now, Calli... Calli recently... had...
You are a lot of fun learning German with me, so you might
You lot are having fun learning German with me, so you might
Fuck you, my characters.
The German question.
Yes, all right.
Spell and you have to do it quickly, okay?
Spell my ending greeting, Auf Wiedersehen!
Go! Start!
Wait, no, shit, damn it!
Oh shit, that's too hard of a question!
I thought this was a Kiara quiz, not a spelling bee!
Chicken!
No, um... I'll give you ten more seconds.
No, it's not arvidachi, it's Auf Wiedersehen!
Come on!
Bonehead!
Wrong!
What the fuck?!
Beep that out, beep that out, whoever's editing this.
Beep that out, whoever's editing this.
It's okay, on my channel it's allowed.
Yeah.
Well, you know what, I said double down, but I'm still gonna treat you for dinner!
Well, I said double down, but I'm still gonna treat you for dinner!
Yay!
Winner, winner, chicken dinner from the chicken, as in the chicken is the dinner's from the chicken...
Winner, winner, chicken dinner from the chicken...
I'll shut the fuck up now. Thank you, Kiara. Happy birthday!
Thank you! I'll read your KFP seal.
Wait, what's the answer? You can't just leave us hanging!
Oh, yeah, okay, it's A-U-F.
Yes, spell it.
Space, W-I-E-D-E-R-S-E-H-E-N!
Auf Wiedersehen!
And we're starting that from now on. Auf Wiedersehen!
Since I just spelled it out, I will say to you girls, Auf Wiedersehen! Next time ask me to spell Shrek.
Happy birthday!
All right, onto the next song. Go!
Uh, let's go!
ドキドキ止まらない もうすぐ 乙女の勇気
My heart won't stop racing, a maiden's courage
ちょっと必要なノックたれ バレンタイン
Just a little necessary knock for Valentine's
甘くてほほ苦い せつない キミへの気持ち
Sweet and slightly bitter, bittersweet feelings for you
make me, maid me コスチュームチェンジ
Make me, maid me, costume change
お気に入りに着替えて！
Change into my favorite outfit!
鼻くすぐる香りに heart ときめいちゃう
The scent tickling my nose makes my heart flutter
let's start 作るよ 愛 込めて
Let's start making it with all my love
とびっきりのチョコレート
A phenomenal chocolate
萌え袖をぎゅっとにぎったら
If I clutch my moe sleeves tightly
mission 開始の合図
It's the signal that the mission begins
カラフルな恋の味
The colorful taste of love
溶けちゃう前に受け取って (please)
Receive it before it melts away (please)
鳴り響く鐘の音 校舎の窓辺でふたり
The ringing bell, the two of us by the classroom window
ねえ はやく言わなくちゃ
Hey, I have to say it soon
照れちゃうけど 「 好きです 」
Even though I'm shy, "I love you"
この想いキミまで届け
Deliver these feelings all the way to you
チクタク進んでいく 気持ちは止められないの
The ticking feelings cannot be stopped
ちょっと勇気出して おくるラブレター
Gathering a little courage, I send a love letter
「 大好き 」 何十回書いても伝えきれない
Writing "I love you" dozens of times isn't enough
make me, fake me 意地悪なのかなんて
Make me, fake me, is it teasing?
空の彼方飛んでけ！
Fly away to the edge of the sky!
何度もチェックして キミに会うときは
Checking over and over, when I meet you
100倍増しで可愛くなりたいの
I want to be 100 times cuter
鏡の前らめっこ いつもと違う sweet さで
Staring into the mirror with a sweetness unlike usual
heart をトリコにしたいの
I want to capture your heart
くるくる変えてみても 髪型まだ決まらない (もうっ！)
Spinning around and changing, my hair still isn't decided (Geez!)
告白のシミュレーション ドキドキさわぎだしちゃう
Confession simulation, my heart is getting restless
月夜に願い込め 一発勝負 明日は絶対に晴れますように
Wishing upon the moon for a one-shot win, hoping tomorrow is sunny
i need to tell you that i love you through and through
there 's no one else in this world that i would trade for you
There's no one else in this world that I would trade for you
萌え袖をぎゅっとにぎったら mission 開始の合図
If I clutch my moe sleeves tightly, it's the signal that the mission begins
カラフルな恋の味 溶けちゃう前に受け取って (please)
The colorful taste of love, receive it before it melts away (please)
鳴り響く鐘の音 校舎の窓辺でふたり
The ringing bell, the two of us by the classroom window
ねえ はやく言わなくちゃ 照れちゃうけど 「 好きです 」
Hey, I have to say it soon, even though I'm shy, "I love you"
この想いキミまで届け
Deliver these feelings all the way to you
チクタク進んでいく 気持ちは止められないの
The ticking feelings cannot be stopped
ちょっと勇気出して おくるラブレター
Gathering a little courage, I send a love letter
「 大好き 」 何十回書いても伝えきれない
Writing "I love you" dozens of times isn't enough
make me, fake me 意地悪なのかなんて
Make me, fake me, is it teasing?
空の彼方飛んでけ！
Fly away to the edge of the sky!
with me! パパン
With me! Papang!
うー！ Hey！
Ooh! Hey!
チクタク進んでいく 気持ちは止められないの
The ticking feelings cannot be stopped
ちょっと勇気出して おくるラブレター
Gathering a little courage, I send a love letter
「大好き」何十回書いても伝えきれない
Writing "I love you" dozens of times isn't enough
make me, fake me 意地悪なのかなんて
Make me, fake me, is it teasing?
空の彼方飛んでけ
Fly away to the edge of the sky!
大好きだよ 何十回書いても
Even if I write "I love you" dozens of times
伝えきれないメイクミ、メイクミ
I can't fully convey it, make me, make me
育児なしなんて
Even without parenting...
空の彼方飛んでけ
Fly away to the edge of the sky!
何度もお茶目にしてキミに会うときは
Checking over and over, when I meet you
百倍増しでかわいくなりたいの
I want to be 100 times cuter
鏡の前見つめ合おう
Staring into each other's eyes in front of the mirror
いつもと違う sweet さで
With a sweetness unlike usual
heart をトリコにしたいの Let's go!
I want to capture your heart. Let's go!
私が薄い一筋で
Lying down on the floor,
あとは取り込みたい
late night and you don't know...
孤独 繰り替えてみても
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right,
髪型 まだ 決まんないの
if yes or no, don't know what to do.
告白のシミュレーション
Gonna make it hot like a volcano,
時々 騒ぎ出す
strike a match and burn it up.
衝動 月より寝返りこめて
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now,
一発勝負 明日は
in the driver's seat strapped.
絶対に晴れますように
So take a step and move it, move it!
And I need to tell you that I love you through and through
There's no one else in this world that I would trade for you
終電で布団ぎゅっと握ったら
Let go of the past tonight,
ミッション開始の合図
choose the future only you define.
カラフルな恋の味
Gonna make it hot like a volcano,
溶けちゃう前に受け取って Please
strike a match and burn it up, please!
鳴り響く鐘の音 高車の窓辺で二人
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today!
ねぇ早く言わなくちゃテレちゃうけど
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now,
好きです。この想い君まで届け
in the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud!
With me, PA-BANG!
Say Wow!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! That was Haruchan, yo!
Remember a while ago at DoKomi where I had backup dancers who were doing the dancing for me?
And now I learned it by myself and performed it myself. Yay!
That was fun. Hope you enjoyed that. Well, you know, if you look at the time, you might think, "Oh, it's going to be over soon."
Nope! There is one more song, but before that, let me say a few words to you guys.
Special, yeah, we're getting close to the end, and I wanted to do something like this for a long time, as you probably know.
And I wanted to show off my dance moves for so long, which is it's one of my, I guess, most prominent skills, and it has been my dream since to start to show it off, to get into this 3D body, finally be free to do whatever I want.
Yeah, and today has finally come. I hope you guys enjoyed it so far.
Yeah, I want to definitely say a big thanks to A-me and Ina and Calliope...
for helping so much with the recording and the setup, you know, A-me basically built a whole studio, you know, for me to record this, and I really, really, really appreciate that.
And without her, it wouldn't have been possible at all.
And also big thanks to Calliope for putting together all of this into a proper concert and even creating this beautiful stage here. Wow, look, isn't it nice?
Yeah, thank you so much! In the future, I really hope that I can do more like this more often and get more members to join me in 3D if possible, to dance together, you know, um, especially, you know, Myth and HoloMyth and their energy.
With all of them, I want to dance and, yeah, have fun together. And I think we're getting there, slowly but surely. Mmm. By the way, if you missed it, the birthday merchandise as announced, it was announced in the stream before this one, the countdown stream.
And it's linked in the description, so please go check it out if you're interested. And yeah, last but not least, I want to thank KFP! You know how much I appreciate your support, and you believing in me and trusting in me means the world to me.
So thank you for giving me the strength in a very, very, very stressful period leading up to this day. Yeah.
And I want to thank,
but I will do that with a song.
So, please listen to the
last song.
Dosou.
ブラック★ロックシューター どこへ行ったの？
Black★Rock Shooter, where did you go?
聞こえますか？
Can you hear me?
あとどれだけ叫ばいいんだろう
How much more should I shout?
あとどれだけ泣けばいいんだろう
How much more should I cry?
もうやめて
Stop it already,
わたしはもう走れない
I can't run anymore.
いつか夢見た世界が閉じる
The world I once dreamed of closes up.
真っ暗で明かりもない
Pitch-black and unlit,
崩れかけたこの道で
on this road that started to crumble,
あるはずもないあのときの希望が見えた気がした
I felt like I could see the hope from back then, which shouldn't exist.
どうして
Why?
ブラック★ロックシューター
Black★Rock Shooter,
懐かしい記憶
they were nostalgic memories,
ただ楽しかったあの頃を
simply of those fun times.
ブラック★ロックシューター
Black★Rock Shooter,
でも動けないよ
but I can't move.
闇をかける星に願いを もう一度だけ走るから
I wish upon the stars shooting through the darkness, because I'll run just once more.
怖くて震える声でつぶやく わたしの名前を呼んで
I'm scared, so I whisper with a trembling voice, "Call my name."
夜明けを抱く空 境界線までの距離 あともう一歩届かない
The sky embracing dawn, the distance to the boundary, I can't reach it in another step.
こらえた涙があふれそうなの 今下を向かないで止まってしまう
Tears that I fought back are about to overflow; now I come to a halt without looking down.
未来を生きていたいんだ わかったの思い出して 強く強く信じるの
Recalling that I know I want to live in the future, I firmly, firmly believe in it!
そうよ
That's right...
ブラック★ロックシューター 優しい匂い
Black★Rock Shooter, there's a tender scent.
痛いよ 辛いよ 飲み込む言葉
"It hurts," "It's tough," I swallow those words!
ブラック★ロックシューター 動いてこの足！
Black★Rock Shooter, move these feet!
世界を超えて！
Overcome the world!
最初から分かっていた ここにいることを
Since the beginning, I've known that I'm here.
私のなかの全ての勇気が火をともして もう逃げないよ！
All of the courage inside of me lights the fire, and I won't flee anymore!
ブラック★ロックシューター ひとりじゃないよ
Black★Rock Shooter, you are not alone!
声を上げて泣いたって構わない
I don't mind even if you cry with a loud voice.
ブラック★ロックシューター 見ていてくれる
Black★Rock Shooter, you'll be watching me.
今から始まるの 私の物語
My story will start from now.
忘そうになったらこの歌を歌うの
When you seem to be forgetting it, I'll sing this song!
今下を向かないで 止まってしまう
Now I come to a halt without looking down.
未来を生きていたいんだ わかったの
I want to live in the future, I figured it out,
思い出して 強く強く信じるの
remember and believe in it strongly, strongly!
そうよ ブラック★ロックシューター
That's right, Black★Rock Shooter,
優しいよ 痛いよ 辛いよ 飲み込む言葉
it's gentle, it hurts, it's tough, words I swallow down.
ブラック★ロックシューター 動いてこの足
Black★Rock Shooter, move these feet,
世界を
the world...
超えて 声を上げて
beyond, raising my voice...
最初からわかっていた ここにいることを
I knew from the very beginning that I am here.
私の中の全ての勇気が火をともして もう逃げないよ
All the courage inside of me lights the fire, I won't run away anymore!
ブラック★ロックシューター ひとりじゃないよ
Black★Rock Shooter, you are not alone!
声を上げて泣いたって構わない
I don't mind even if you cry with a loud voice.
ブラック★ロックシューター 見ていてくれる 今から始まるの
Black★Rock Shooter, watching over me, it starts right now,
私の物語
my story.
gotta make it hot like a volcano